http://www.fiberglas.org/privacy-policy

Skip to main contentSkip to footerDocuments in Portable Document Format (PDF) require Adobe Acrobat Reader 5.0 or higher to view,download Adobe® Acrobat Reader.
Toggle navigation Toggle navigation Toggle navigation MenuEnter search terms Search icon Search submit
Savings and Checking
Why Save With Us?
Savings Calculators
Savings Rates
Checking Accounts
Debit Cards
TruePerks Rewards
IRAs
Share Certificates
Change It Up
The Credit Union Difference
Privacy Policy What Does TrueCore Federal Credit Union Do With Your Personal Information?
Rev. Date 5/20/2019
Why?
Financial companies choose how they share your personal information. Federal law gives consumers the right to limit some, but not all sharing. Federal law also requires us to tell you how we collect, share, and protect your personal information. Please read this notice carefully to understand what we do.
What?
The types of personal information we collect and share depend on the product or service you have with us. This information can include:
Social security number and overdraft history
Credit history and credit scores
Payment history and transaction history
When you are no longer our member, we continue to share your information as described in this notice.
How?
All financial companies need to share members’ personal information to run their everyday business. In the section below, we list the reasons financial companies can share their members’ personal information, the reasons TrueCore Federal Credit Union chooses to share, and whether you can limit this sharing.
Reasons We Can Share Your Personal Information
Does TrueCore Federal Credit Union share?
Can you limit this sharing?
For our everyday business purposes
– such as to process your transactions, maintain your account(s), respond to court orders and legal investigations, or to report to credit bureaus
Yes
No
For our marketing purposes
– to offer our products and services to you
Yes
No
For joint marketing with other financial companies
Yes
We don't share
Questions?
Call 740-345-6608 or go to www.truecore.org
What We Do
How does TrueCore Federal Credit Union protect my personal information?
To protect your personal information from unauthorized access and use, we use security measures that comply with federal law. These measures include computer safeguards and secured files and buildings.
How does TrueCore Federal Credit Union collect my personal information?
We collect your personal information, for example, when you
open an account or deposit or show your government-issued ID
apply for financing or give us your contact information
give us your wage statements
We also collect your personal information from others, such as credit bureaus, affiliates, or other companies.
Why can’t I limit all sharing?
Federal law gives you the right to limit only
sharing for affiliates’ everyday business purposes –information about your creditworthiness
affiliates from using your information to market to you
sharing for nonaffiliates to market to you
State law and individual companies may give you additional rights to limit sharing. See below for more on your rights under state law.
Definitions
Affiliates
Companies related by common ownership or control. They can be financial and nonfinancial companies.
- TrueCore Federal Credit Union has no affiliates.
Nonaffiliates
Companies not related by common ownership or control. They can be financial and non-financial companies.
- TrueCore Federal Credit Union does not share with our nonaffiliates so they can market to you.
Joint Marketing
A formal agreement between nonaffiliated financial companies that together market financial products or services to you.
- Our joint marketing partners include CUNA Mutual Group's MEMBERCONNECT and loan recapture programs.
